//creating an array and passing the number, question, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question:"Who did Kylian Mbappe take over as the Monaco's youngest ever goalscorer?",
        answer: "Thierry Henry",
        options:[
            "Bruno Bellone",
            "Thomas Lemar",
            "Thierry Henry",
            "David Trezeguet"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question:"Which of the Arsenal strikers has scored the most Ligue 1 goals?",
        answer: "Marouane Chamakh",
        options:[
            "Marouane Chamakh",
            "Gervinho",
            "Olivier Giroud",
            "Pierre-Emerick Aubameyang"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question:"Who is the highest goal scorer of the league 1 history?",
        answer: "Delio Onnis",
        options:[
            "Herve Revelli",
            "Roger Courtois",
            "Delio Onnis",
            "Bernard Lacombe"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question:"Which team has won the Ligue 1 most sucssecive times(7)?(2002-2008)",
        answer: "Olmpique Lyonnais",
        options:[
            "Olmpique Lyonnais",
            "Paris Saint-German",
            "AS Saint-Etienne",
            "Olympique de Marseille"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question:"Which Ligue 1 team has won the champions league?",
        answer: "Marseille",
        options:[
            "Paris-saint-german",
            "Marseille",
            "Lyon",
            "AS Saint-Etienne"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question:"Who is the official sponsor of Ligue 1?",
        answer: "Uber eats",
        options:[
            "Barclays",
            "Santandar",
            "Nike",
            "Uber eats"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question:"Which year was the french football league first played?",
        answer: "1893-94",
        options:[
            "1893-94",
            "1901-1902",
            "2001-2003",
            "1887-1888"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question:"Who is the official Champion of first ever french football league?",
        answer: "Standard Athletic Club",
        options:[
            "The White Rovers",
            "Club Francais",
            "Le Havre",
            "Standard Athletic Club"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question:"What was the score when Lyon hosted Marseille in November 2009?",
        answer: "Lyon 5-5 Marseille",
        options:[
            "Lyon 4-4 Marseille",
            "Lyon 5-6 Marseille",
            "Lyon 5-5 Marseille",
            "Lyon 4-5 Marseille"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question:"How many goals has Zlatan Ibrahimovic scored in Ligue 1?",
        answer: "156",
        options:[
            "124",
            "156",
            "158",
            "143"
        ]
    },
];